revolutionofgaming.com 2011-04-07

# Privacy Policy

infos

Sunday, 01 August 2010 18:17 

**Renegade Gaming**

**Privacy Policy**

**July 11, 2009**

Renegade Gaming (“RG”) recognizes that privacy is important.  This Policy applies to all websites and services offered by RG.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our webmaster at [webmaster@renegadegaming.com](mailto:webmaster@renegadegaming.com).

**Information we collect and how we use it**

Although we offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, in order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

  * **Information you provide** – When you sign up for a website account or other RG service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password).

  * **Website cookies** – When you visit renegadegaming.com, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, most renegadegaming.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

  * **Log information** – When you use RG services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

  * **User communications** – When you send email, private message or other communication to RG, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

  * **Affiliated sites** – We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to RG in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

  * **Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by RG. We do not exercise control over the sites that link from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

RG only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services.  In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our services to users, including the display of customized content;
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and
  * Developing new services.

**Choices for personal information**

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information.  If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes.  We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case RG may not be able to provide those services to you.

**Information sharing**

RG only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of RG in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent.  We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of RG, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If RG becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement.  Such information does not identify you individually.

Please contact us through our webmaster at [webmaster@renegadegamingonline.com](mailto:webmaster@renegadegamingonline.com) for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to RG employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.  These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.  RG employees, contractors, and agents will NEVER ask you for your password.   Any requests for your password should be reported to the administration immediately.

**Data integrity**

RG processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice.  We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services.  We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

**Accessing and updating personal information**

When you use RG services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.  We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required.  In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

**Enforcement**

RG regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy.  Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or RG’s treatment of personal information by contacting us through our webmaster at [webmaster@renegadegaming.com](mailto:webmaster@renegadegaming.com).  When we receive formal written complaints, it is RG’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns.  We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between RG and an individual.
